aaspaas.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

The website under the URL www.aaspaas.com and the services provided through the “aaspaas” service, software and tools are owned, operated and maintained by Xen Webhosting Private Limited(“XEN WEBHOSTING”)/("SANGWAN"). 

Sangwan is very keen on safeguarding your personal privacy.   
"Xen Webhosting Private Limited" does not sell any information to any telemarketing, direct marketing or commercial mass e-mail companies, agents or representatives.

The policy prohibits the use of information contained in aaspaas.com directory database from use by third parties such as telemarketing, direct marketing, commercial mass e-mail companies, agents or representatives and e-mail spammers.

In some areas of our website, as well as for purposes of subscription, download and use of the aaspaas services, software and tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us, or accordingly other users of the aaspaas service, to enhance your site visit, reply to you after your visit or to fully utilise the aaspaas services, software and tools. This would include where you download software, subscribe to services or provide feedback. When you do so we ask you to give us your name, address and email address. The information you provide will be kept confidential. The information will be used by us and other aaspaas users in accordance with the aaspaas’s Terms and Conditions of Service. Otherwise the information will be kept confidential. 

We may use your personal data for future email mailings, support, notification of new services, general correspondence regarding our services and correspondence which may relate to you. If in the future you do not wish to receive future marketing emails from us please inform us by email at unsubsrcibe@aaspaas.com. 

We do use cookies for collecting user information from the site or for purposes of the aaspaas services and information about you will be collected solely for purposes of system administration, for purposes of the aaspaas services and otherwise as described above and in accordance with the aaspaas’s Terms and Conditions of Service. Cookies are messages given to a web browser by a web server. The message is then stored by the browser in a text file called “cookie.txt”. Each time the browser requests a page from the server, this message is sent back. A cookie’s main objective is to identify users. A service using cookies will usually invite you to provide personal information such as your name and email address. 

**While you visit our site, you may be providing certain information:**   
a) Anonymous statistics concerning pages searched.   
b) Personal information that you knowingly give us.   
c) Anonymous statistics concerning click through ads. 

**About your visit with aaspaas.com:**   
In an effort to provide maximum benefit to you, the user, we collect information, not about you personally, but about your visit. We are constantly monitoring information such as:  
a) The number of visits to our site.  
b) Which pages are the more popular than others are.  
c) From which domains our visitors come from.  
d) From which areas of the country or foreign country our visitors come from.  
e) Which browsers are more popular with visitors to our site.  
f) What days and times of day are most active.   Again, this information is not associated with you as an individual.

**Data Information**

The data contained in our database is derived from two sources:   
a)  Contractual relationships with database companies to provide information from local publishers, phone books, new business filings and other assorted sources.   
b)  Businesses who list, modify, update or enhance their listings.   
c)  Businesses who advertise with category display advertisements.   
For further information on data protection and personal privacy, and to change any of the details we hold about you may contact the data controller which is Netquest. Our corporate details, address and other contact details can be found below. 

See also our Terms and Conditions.
